<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="account">Konto</string>
    <string name="app_icon">App-Symbol</string>
    <string name="welcome">Willkommen</string>
    <string name="start_chat">Chat beginnen</string>
    <string name="welcome_to">Willkommen bei</string>
    <string name="welcome_app_name">Aikonia 👋</string>
    <string name="welcome_description">Beginne jetzt zu chatten mit Lynn.\nDu kannst mich alles fragen</string>
    <string name="ask_me_anything">Frag mich alles was du möchtest.</string>
    <string name="back_icon">Zurück-Symbol</string>
    <string name="share">Teilen</string>
    <string name="writing">Schreiben</string>
    <string name="write_article">Artikel schreiben</string>
    <string name="write_article_description">Erstelle gut geschriebene Artikel zu jedem Thema, das du möchtest</string>
    <string name="academic_writer">Akademischer Schreiber</string>
    <string name="academic_writer_description">Erstelle Bildungstexte wie Aufsätze, Berichte usw.</string>
    <string name="summarize">Zusammenfassen (TL;DR)</string>
    <string name="summarize_description">Hebe die Hauptpunkte aus langen Texten hervor.</string>
    <string name="translate_language">Sprache übersetzen</string>
    <string name="translate_language_description">Übersetze von einer Sprache in eine andere</string>
    <string name="plagiarism_checker">Plagiatsprüfung</string>
    <string name="plagiarism_checker_description">Überprüfe den Originalitätsgrad des Textes</string>
    <string name="creative">Kreativ</string>
    <string name="song_lyrics">Lieder / Texte</string>
    <string name="song_lyrics_description">Erstelle Texte für jede Musikrichtung, die du möchtest.</string>
    <string name="storyteller">Geschichtenerzähler</string>
    <string name="storyteller_description">Erstelle Geschichten zu jedem gegebenen Thema.</string>
    <string name="poems">Gedichte</string>
    <string name="poems_description">Erstelle Gedichte in verschiedenen Stilen</string>
    <string name="movie_script">Filmskript</string>
    <string name="movie_script_description">Erstelle das Skript für einen Film</string>
    <string name="email_writer">E-Mail-Schreiber</string>
    <string name="email_writer_description">Erstelle Vorlagen für E-Mails, Briefe usw.</string>
    <string name="answer_interviewer">Interview-Antworter</string>
    <string name="answer_interviewer_description">Erstelle Antworten auf Interviewfragen.</string>
    <string name="job_post">Stellenanzeige</string>
    <string name="job_post_description">Schreibe ideale Stellenbeschreibungen für Anzeigen.</string>
    <string name="advertisement">Werbung</string>
    <string name="advertisement_description">Erstelle Werbetexte für Produkte, Dienstleistungen, Marken usw.</string>
    <string name="business">Geschäft</string>
    <string name="social_media">Soziale Medien</string>
    <string name="linkedin">LinkedIn</string>
    <string name="linkedin_description">Erstelle auffällige Beiträge auf LinkedIn</string>
    <string name="instagram">Instagram</string>
    <string name="instagram_description">Schreibe Bildunterschriften, die auf Instagram Aufmerksamkeit erregen.</string>
    <string name="twitter">Twitter</string>
    <string name="twitter_description">Verfasse Tweets, die auf Twitter Aufmerksamkeit erregen.</string>
    <string name="tiktok">TikTok</string>
    <string name="tiktok_description">Erstelle auffällige und virale Bildunterschriften auf TikTok</string>
    <string name="facebook">Facebook</string>
    <string name="facebook_description">Erstelle auffällige Beiträge auf Facebook</string>
    <string name="developer">Entwickler</string>
    <string name="write_code">Code schreiben</string>
    <string name="write_code_description">Schreibe Codes in jeder Programmiersprache.</string>
    <string name="explain_code">Code erklären</string>
    <string name="explain_code_description">Erkläre komplizierte Programmcode-Schnipsel</string>
    <string name="personal">Persönlich</string>
    <string name="birtday">Geburtstag</string>
    <string name="birtday_description">Erstelle aufrichtige Geburtstagswünsche für deine Liebsten</string>
    <string name="apology">Entschuldigung</string>
    <string name="apology_description">Formuliere eine Entschuldigung für begangene Fehler</string>
    <string name="invitation">Einladung</string>
    <string name="invitation_description">Schreibe perfekte Einladungen für jedes Event</string>
    <string name="other">Andere</string>
    <string name="create_conversation">Gespräch erstellen</string>
    <string name="create_conversation_description">Erstelle Gesprächsvorlagen für zwei oder mehr Personen</string>
    <string name="tell_joke">Erzähle einen Witz</string>
    <string name="tell_joke_description">Schreibe lustige Witze, um deine Freunde zum Lachen zu bringen.</string>
    <string name="food_recipes">Kochrezepte</string>
    <string name="food_recipes_description">Erhalte Kochrezepte für Speisen.</string>
    <string name="diet_plan">Ernährungsplan</string>
    <string name="diet_plan_description">Erstelle Mahlzeitenpläne und Diäten basierend auf deinen Vorlieben.</string>
    <string name="all">Alle</string>
    <string name="capabilities">Fähigkeiten</string>
    <string name="capabilities_1">Beantworte all deine Fragen.\n(Frag mich einfach, was du möchtest!)</string>
    <string name="capabilities_2"><![CDATA[Erzeuge allen Text, den du möchtest.\n(Aufsätze, Artikel, Berichte, Geschichten & mehr)]]></string>
    <string name="capabilities_3">Konversationelle KI\n(Ich kann mit dir sprechen wie ein echter Mensch)</string>
    <string name="capabilities_desc">Das sind nur einige Beispiele, was ich tun kann</string>
    <string name="stop_generating">Generierung stoppen…</string>
    <string name="copy">Kopieren</string>
<string name="write_article_example1">Write an article discussing the benefits of practicing mindfulness in daily life</string>
<string name="write_article_example2">Write an article discussing the impact of climate change on the planet.</string>
<string name="write_article_example3">Write an article discussing the importance of maintaining a healthy work-life balance.</string>
<string name="academic_writer_example1">Write an academic essay about the impact of climate change on global food security.</string>
<string name="academic_writer_example2">Write an academic essay about the role of technology in shaping modern education.</string>
<string name="academic_writer_example3">Write an academic essay about the ethics of artificial intelligence and its impact on society.</string>
<string name="summarize_example1">Summarize this article \"The effectiveness of cognitive-behavioral therapy in treating depression.....</string>
<string name="summarize_example2">Summarize this essay \"An analysis of the impact of social media on mental health.</string>
<string name="summarize_example3">Summarize this story \"An Old Man in the Village..</string>
<string name="translate_language_example1">Translate the following sentences into English \"Consejos para mantenerse motivado y productivo mientras trabaja desde casa.\"</string>
<string name="translate_language_example2">Translate the following sentences into German \"心理健康和自我保健对整体福祉的重要性\"</string>
<string name="translate_language_example3">Translate the following sentences into Korean \"Impactul schimbárilor climatice asupra securitátii alimentare globale.</string>
<string name="plagiarism_checker_example1">I want to check the plagiarism of this article \"Social media has completely transformed the way we communicate and interact</string>
<string name="plagiarism_checker_example2">What is the level of originality of this essay \"One of the ways globalization has contributed to income inequality is</string>
<string name="plagiarism_checker_example3">What percentage level of plagiarism emerges from this thesis \"Globalization has been a driving</string>
<string name="song_lyrics_example1">Make me lyrics of a broken heart because of love</string>
<string name="song_lyrics_example2">want to make a song with the theme of true friends</string>
<string name="song_lyrics_example3">Make me a rock song with an anti-war subject</string>
<string name="storyteller_example1">Make me a bedtime story about a girl with a magic stone</string>
<string name="storyteller_example2">I want to make a short novel story about a friendship in high school</string>
<string name="storyteller_example3">want to write a short story about the meaning of love and friends</string>
<string name="poems_example1">Make me a poems with the theme of justice and social criticism</string>
<string name="poems_example2">I want to write a poems about divinity</string>
<string name="poems_example3">I want to write a poem on the subject of failure in life and rising to success</string>
<string name="movie_script_example1">Give me a script for a comedy set in an amusement park</string>
<string name="movie_script_example2">want to write a short film script about life and friends in high school</string>
<string name="movie_script_example3">Make me a romance-themed film script with a background in the 80s in Europe</string>
<string name="email_writer_example1">Write me a cover letter for the Product Designer position at Google company.</string>
<string name="email_writer_example2">I want to write an email to the boss that I can not enter the office due to illness.</string>
<string name="email_writer_example3">Write me a template email message to my customers that I have an exciting new product.</string>
<string name="answer_interviewer_example1">Give me the answer to the interview question \"What salary do you want?\"</string>
<string name="answer_interviewer_example2">What is the best answer to the interview question \"What motivates you to work for this company?\"</string>
<string name="answer_interviewer_example3">Give me a way to answer the interview question \"What contribution can you make to the company?\"</string>
<string name="job_post_example1">Make me a job post with the position of Product Designer for my company.</string>
<string name="job_post_example2">want to write a job post for a new employee in my office</string>
<string name="job_post_example3">Give me a short but interesting job post for a researcher position for a research project</string>
<string name="advertisement_example1">I have a salon service, give me advertising words for marketing purposes on social media</string>
<string name="advertisement_example2">Give me advertisements for perfume products that I just released to attract buyers</string>
<string name="advertisement_example3">Write me an advertisement for food bazaar event and big discount on sunday</string>
<string name="linkedin_example1">I need a Linkedin post idea that showcases my programs and its unique value proposition to my audience clearly and concisely.</string>
<string name="linkedin_example2">I\'m looking for a Linkedln post idea that shares a recent success story with my service and highlights its positive impact on my customer</string>
<string name="linkedin_example3">Can you help me develop a Linkedin post idea that features a testimonial from one of my client and how my product helped solve their specific problem?</string>
<string name="instagram_example1">I\'m looking for an Instagram post idea that will showcase the unique features and benefits of my product and convince my customer to make a purchase.</string>
<string name="instagram_example2">need an Instagram post idea that will highlight the social proof and positive reviews of my service to build trust and credibility with my target audience.</string>
<string name="instagram_example3">I\'m looking for an Instagram post idea that will educate my audience on the benefits and uses of my service in a creative and engaging way.</string>
<string name="twitter_example1">I need a tweet idea to promote my online course product for the ideal customer on twitter to buy it</string>
<string name="twitter_example2">need an tweet idea that will tell the story behind my company and its mission to connect with my target audience on a personal level.</string>
<string name="twitter_example3">I\'m looking for an tweet post idea that will feature user-generated content and showcase how my product is making a difference in the lives of real people.</string>
<string name="tiktok_example1">need a TikTok caption post idea that will showcase my novel ebook in action through a demo video or product tutorial.</string>
<string name="tiktok_example2">I\'m looking for a caption tiktok post idea that will tap into the current trending topics and relate it to my cosmetic product in a fun and entertaining way.</string>
<string name="tiktok_example3">I\'m looking for a TikTok caption post idea that will ask a question to my audience and encourage them to engage in the comments section.</string>
<string name="facebook_example1">I need a Facebook post idea that will showcase my digital product in action with real-life examples of how it has benefited my customers.</string>
<string name="facebook_example2">I need a Facebook post idea that will share a personal experience or success story related to my design course and inspire my audience.</string>
<string name="facebook_example3">I need a Facebook post idea that will introduce my ebook in an attention-grabbing way and highlight its unique features that differentiate it from competitors.</string>
<string name="write_code_example1">Give me a CRUD function in Python programming language</string>
<string name="write_code_example2">How do I make an HTTP request in Javascript, PH, and Python?</string>
<string name="write_code_example3">Locate any logic errors in the following [language] code snippet: [code snippet].</string>
<string name="explain_code_example1">I have the PHP code, but I don\'t know what it means. Can you explain this code \"Paste your code here\"</string>
<string name="explain_code_example2">Can you explain this code, find logic errors, and potential performance issues if any \"Paste your code here\"</string>
<string name="explain_code_example3">Describe the function of this code, find deadlock issues, and potential SQL injection vulnerabilities if any \"Paste your code here\"</string>
<string name="birtday_example1">Write me a heartfelt wish for my daughter\'s 12th birthday</string>
<string name="birtday_example2">Iwant to wish my mother a sincere happy birthday who will be 60 years old</string>
<string name="birtday_example3">Write me a sincere wish for my boyfriend who has a birthday tomorrow</string>
<string name="apology_example1">I disappointed friends by forgetting an important appointment, can I make a sincere apology?</string>
<string name="apology_example2">I made my mother angry, write me a sincere apology</string>
<string name="apology_example3">I dropped my girlfriend Sarah\'s favorite cosmetics, what should I say to apologize?</string>
<string name="invitation_example1">I have a talk show event on Saturday night, can I make an invitation for me to share with my audience?</string>
<string name="invitation_example2">I\'m having my l6th birthday, I want to make an invitation for my childhood friend Mage.</string>
<string name="invitation_example3">I want to make a dinner party with my high school friends, please make me an invitation to give them.</string>
<string name="create_conversation_example1">Write me a conversation between 4 people discussing tourist destinations in America</string>
<string name="create_conversation_example2"><![CDATA[Do me a two person conversation between John & Lily about attending a school reunion.]]></string>
<string name="create_conversation_example3">Give me a short conversation between three people discussing quantum physics.</string>
<string name="tell_joke_example1">Tell me a joke about lion</string>
<string name="tell_joke_example2">Throw me some high school jokes</string>
<string name="tell_joke_example3">Write me 5 jokes about giraffes for me to tell my friends.</string>
<string name="food_recipes_example1">I want to eat a salad, give me a simple salad recipe with the main ingredients avocado, cabbage, tomatoes and carrots.</string>
<string name="food_recipes_example2">Give me a recipe for making Korean oriental Paieon that\'s not so spicy.</string>
<string name="food_recipes_example3">Give me an Italian food recipe that is low in fat and cholesterol.</string>
<string name="diet_plan_example1">I weigh 80 kg, I want a diet plan to eat vegetables without avocado and cabbage because I hate it.</string>
<string name="diet_plan_example2">I want a fruit diet plan without pineapple and papaya for 1 full month.</string>
<string name="diet_plan_example3">Put me on a nut, tomato and fish free diet plan because I\'m allergic to them.</string>
<string name="type_something_like">Type something like:</string>
    <string name="empty">Leer</string>
    <string name="no_history">Du hast keinen Chatverlauf.</string>
    <string name="clear_all_history">Gesamten Chatverlauf löschen</string>
    <string name="are_you_sure_delete_all_history">Bist du sicher, dass du den gesamten Chatverlauf löschen möchtest?</string>
    <string name="cancel">Abbrechen</string>
    <string name="yes_clear_all">Ja, löschen</string>
    <string name="search_conversation">Suche im Chatverlauf…</string>
    <string name="upgrade_to_pro">Auf PRO upgraden!</string>
    <string name="upgrade_to_pro_description">Genieße alle Vorteile ohne Einschränkungen</string>
    <string name="language">Sprache</string>
    <string name="general">Allgemein</string>
    <string name="dark_theme">Dunkler Modus</string>
    <string name="help_center">Hier findest du Hilfe</string>
    <string name="about">Über die App</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy">Datenschutzrichtlinie</string>
    <string name="about_us">Über Aikonia</string>
    <string name="logout">Abmelden</string>
    <string name="are_you_sure_logout">Bist du sicher, dass du dich abmelden möchtest?</string>
    <string name="yes_logout">Ja, abmelden</string>
    <string name="settings">Einstellungen</string>
    <string name="restore_purchase">Kauf wiederherstellen</string>
    <string name="purchase">Kaufen</string>
    <string name="pro">PRO</string>
    <string name="powered_by_chat_gpt">Angetrieben von Aikonias Magie</string>
    <string name="remove_ads">Werbung entfernen</string>
    <string name="unlimited_messages">Unbegrenzte Nachrichten</string>
    <string name="cancel_anytime">Jederzeit kündbar</string>
    <string name="restore">Wiederherstellen</string>
    <string name="weekly">Wöchentlich</string>
    <string name="monthly">Monatlich</string>
    <string name="yearly">Jährlich</string>
    <string name="per_week">Pro Woche</string>
    <string name="per_month">Pro Monat</string>
    <string name="per_year">Pro Jahr</string>
    <string name="save85">85 % sparen</string>
    <string name="secured_by_google_play">Gesichert durch Google Play. Jederzeit kündbar</string>
    <string name="watch_ad">Kurze Werbung ansehen</string>
    <string name="you_reach_free_message_limit">Du hast leider das tägliche Limit kostenloser Nachrichten erreicht. Du kannst auf die PRO-Version upgraden oder eine weitere kostenlose Nachricht erhalten, indem du eine kurze Werbung ansiehst.</string>
    <string name="welcome_to_pro_version">Willkommen in der Pro-Version!</string>
    <string name="pro_version_not_purchased">Pro-Version nicht gekauft</string>
    <string name="network_error">Netzwerkfehler</string>
    <string name="no_conection_try_again">Bitte verbinde dich mit dem Internet und versuche es erneut.</string>
    <string name="update">Neu laden</string>
    <string name="there_is_new_version">Es gibt eine neue Version dieser App, bitte aktualisiere sie</string>
</resources>
